http://www.iristhedragon.com/terms-of-use.html/#privacy-policy

CANADA / USA JURISDICTION
General Terms and ConditionsPlease read the following information to understand what rights are reserved for Iris the Dragon and for visitors using this site.JurisdictionIris the Dragon is based in in Perth, Ontario, Canada and operates this web site in compliance within Canadian and American federal guidelines.Iris the Dragon also recognizes the EU's General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and our organization's requirement to comply with aspects of the legislation.Communications IntentThe intent of this Iris the Dragon communications product (web site) is to promote mental health wellness. The business-to-consumer (B2C) and business-to-business (B2B) communication extends to Iris the Dragon's social media spaces.Content Copyright NoticeIris the Dragon owns the rights to all content in this site. All content is protected under U.S. and Canadian copyright law which is enforceable worldwide. Copyright © Iris The Dragon, 2018. All Rights Reserved.Copyright ExclusionsIris the Dragon does offer resources and tools developed by other organizations. These items are copyright of the owner.Website Visitors from Outside North AmericaWe can't tell you if the materials in this site are appropriate or available for use outside of our jurisdiction but we do know that online visitors from other countries explore it. Consequently, if you're from outside of North America, make sure you know about and comply with any applicable local laws that apply to the Internet and the World Wide Web.Intellectual Property OwnershipIP belongs to the originator of any real or conceptual offering on this website be it ideas, code, text, artwork, audio-video, royalty-free objects, etc.You may not use any of the text or graphics on your own web site or in any other public or commercial manner unless promoting Iris the Dragon and in the spirit of social media sharing. You may not reverse-engineer, disassemble or otherwise convert our content into another form to mask its ownership.TrademarksUnless otherwise specified, all trademarks used on this site are the property of Iris the Dragon or their partners. Other company and product brands may be identified in this site and Iris the Dragon exercises diligence to ensure proper use and representation.Submissions and the Expectation of PrivacyPlease refer to our Privacy Policy. Iris the Dragon cannot be held responsible for data illegally intercepted during transmission. Information and files submitted online are encrypted during transmission and Iris the Dragon assures reasonable confidentiality in managing your data once it is received. Iris the Dragon also assures that personal data submitted for any service such as newsletter membership will not be distributed, leased, sold, or otherwise made available outside of Iris the Dragon unless stated or authorized to do so.Use of Public Areas on this SiteYour use of any public areas on this site (such as discussion forums, chat areas, and submission pages) is subject to special rules. Those rules will be posted on the relevant page and are incorporated by reference into this Agreement. Any violation of our public area rules constitutes a violation of the Terms of Use.Limitation of Liability and DisclaimerNeither Iris the Dragon or its agents, nor anyone who helped develop, create, produce or deliver the material and information in this site are liable for any damages related to your use of or inability to use the site. This includes, but is not limited to: damages intended to compensate you directly for any loss or injury; damages reasonably expected to result from any loss or injury (consequential damages); other miscellaneous damages and expenses resulting directly from a loss or injury (incidental damages); and/or punitive damages.You agree that we are not liable even if Iris the Dragon, any of its agents, or an authorized representative of the company has been negligent, or if either has been advised of the possibility of such damages.We use our best efforts to provide accurate information, but do not guarantee it, and make no representations regarding the use or results of use of any materials in this site in terms of their accuracy, reliability or any other matter. We do not guarantee that this site or every feature of this site will remain available to you.Iris the Dragon and its agents do not warrant that the functions contained in the site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, that this site or any server that makes it available is free from viruses or other harmful components, or that successful results or outcomes will result from your use of information at this site.Without limiting the foregoing, all information on this site is provided "as is," without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, any implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. Some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties — please check local laws.In no event shall our total liability to you for any and all losses, damages, and/or causes of action, whether in contract, tort or otherwise, exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing this site.Iris the Dragon is not responsible for any material posted by any user or for any information whatsoever contained in any linked sites. You expressly acknowledge and agree that Iris the Dragon and its affiliates are not responsible or liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any other visitor to this site or any other third party.TerminationYou may terminate this Agreement at any time by ceasing to use this site and removing (deleting) from your local system all information obtained from this site with any related documentation and copies. Iris the Dragon may terminate this Agreement at any time without notice if you breach any term or condition of this Agreement, including any term or condition of our public area rules. We reserve the right to pursue any remedy available to us at law or equity for your violation of this Agreement.OtherThis constitutes the entire agreement between the parties. If any provision of this Agreement is found to be void, unlawful or unenforceable for any reason, that portion shall be deemed severable from these terms and shall not otherwise affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. Iris the Dragon reserves the right to change this Agreement, and your continued use of this site after that time shall constitute your acceptance of any new terms thereafter.© Iris the Dragon 2018. All Rights Reserved.
PRIVACY POLICY
CANADA / USA COMPLIANCE
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in U.S. privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.Please visit the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada and Canada's Anti-spam Law for privacy protection information. We also encourage you to Download the Handbook for Safeguarding Sensitive Personally Identifiable Information  produced by the U.S. Department of Homeland Security. It offers good explanations and practical advice on safeguarding personal data.The purpose of this web site is both Business to Consumer (B2C) and Business to Business (B2B)Iris the Dragon is a registered Canadian charity focused on the development and promotion of mental health resources and tools and is therefore only interested in communicating with persons and organizations seeking to access these resources or to partner on projects.What personal information do we collect from people that visit our website?The only PII we collect is that which you voluntarily offer in order for us to contact you or to register you for services. We may also ask for information in order to help you with your experience while online.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you fill out a form, use a Live Chat function or enter information on our site.How do we use your information? We may use the information you offer us and that we collect when you fill in a contact form, sign up for our newsletter, make a purchase, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: to follow up with you after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries); and to send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect your information?Our website is hosted on a monitored network. We scan for Malware monthly via Google's Transparency Report.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, any sensitive or credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.We use cookies to:Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Some features may be disabled if you turn cookies off but it shouldn't affect your overall experience.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide website visitors with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our visitors, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it is required to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or to protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GoogleWe use Google Analytics to collect and aggregate data about the user experience on our website. This service does not reveal personally identifiable information — the exception being "referral links" from websites and social media accounts clearly bearing the personal name of the operator. We are primarily concerned with the following: Demographics and Interests Reporting; Referral Traffic; Preferred Browser and Device Use; and Website Engagement / Analytic Paths.We do not use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. We encourage those interested in online privacy to read up on How Google uses cookies in advertising. Google's Advertising Principles are located at https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en. Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. Details at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufWe agree to the following with respect to the CalOPPA: Users can visit our site anonymously. Providing visitors with a link to this privacy policy on our home page. The link includes the word "privacy" as does page title or header. Visitors will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on this Privacy Policy page.You can change personal information that you voluntarily offered us by contacting us through email:Subject line: Attn: Iris the Dragon Privacy Officer — Change of PII Requestinfo@iristhedragon.comHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?Our website service detects 'Do Not Track' signals and, accordingly, does not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when DNT is requested.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?We do however, allow third-party behavioral tracking such as is the case with Google Analytics.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. While many of our resources are designed for young people, we do not market to children under the age of 13 years.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days.We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. We collect your email address in order to: Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following: Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses. Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way. Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters. Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used. Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly. Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@iristhedragon.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting UsPlease contact us by email if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy:Subject line: Attn: Iris the Dragon Privacy Officerinfo@iristhedragon.comLast Edited on 2018-02-11
Contact us now
* Indicates required field
Name *
First
Last
Email *
I would like to enquire about... *
Iris the Dragon Books
Submit
Iris the Dragon613-264-723410 Perkins Boulevard, Perth, Ontario, K7H 3L6, CanadaRegistered Canadian charity #81398 5017 RR 0001All Rights Reserved, © 2019 Iris the Dragon
HOME | BOOKSTORE |  | FOR SCHOOLS | FOR WORKPLACES | FOR COMMUNITIES | ABOUT | MEDIA | TERMS OF USE | PRIVACY POLICY
